Archishman Ghosh

9674629474 | ag2324@it.jgec.ac.in | linkedin/Archishman Ghosh| Personal Site

ABOUT

I am a student at Jalpaiguri Government Engineering College, pursuing my BTech in Information Technology and have been a competitive programmer for 2 years. I am also an android development enthusiast and have been learning flutter since a month. In my pastime, I am a petrol-head and tech-enthusiast.

EDUCATION

Jalpaiguri Government Engineering College

Bachelor of Technology in Information Technology, Secured an aggregate of 7.64 CGPA

Army Public School Kolkata, India

Central Board of Secondary Examination, secured a percentage of 87.4

Ram Mohan Mission High School

Indian Certificate of Secondary Education, secured a percentage of 96

Experience

World-Time App | Dart, Flutter

April 2021

Kolkata, India

Jalpaiguri, India

Aug. 2019 - Present

Aug. 2016 - Mar. 2018

Apr. 2004 - Apr. 2016

- Developed a World-Time app using flutter, which shows the time at various locations around the world
- Learnt how to fetch api and implement the same

Brew Crew | Dart, Flutter, Firebase

April 2021

- Developed a coffee ordering system, wherein the user can mention exactly what type of coffee he needs, including the amount of ingredients
- Learnt firebase and authentication service, where a user can either register or sign in to use the app

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Got a Global Rank of 207 out of 14500 contestants in Codechef's November Long Challenge 2020.
- Got a Global rank of 1125 and India rank of 63 out of 18000 contestants in Codeforces Round 706.
- Got a Global Rank of 2699 in Kickstart Round G 2020 hosted by Google.
- Got a Global Rank of 111 in M-Code hosted by IIEST, Shibpur.
- Highest rating of 1882 (4 star) and 1490 (Specialist) at Codechef and Codeforces respectively.
- Solved more than 1800 problems on various online coding judges.

SKILLS

• C++, Dart for Flutter, elementary Java, elementary Python

Languages

Bengali Mother tongue

English Fluent Hindi Fluent

PROFILES

- Codechef/archishmanghos
- Codeforces/Archi
- Atcoder/archishmanghos
- HackerRank/archishmanghos
- Github/archishmanghos